<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<person>
	<personID>A5011859104</personID>
	<FullName>Naomi Fukagawa</FullName>
	<FirstName>Naomi</FirstName>
	<LastName>Fukagawa</LastName>
	<publication>
		<title>Strength Is a Major Factor in Balance, Gait, and the Occurrence of Falls</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Leslie Wolfson, J. Judge, Robert Whipple, Laurie A. King</authors>
		<jconf>The Journals of Gerontology Series A</jconf>
		<id>W2013160037</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Rice: Importance for Global Nutrition</title>
		<year>2019</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Lewis H. Ziska</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Nutritional Science and Vitaminology</jconf>
		<id>W2981007357</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Insulin-mediated reduction of whole body protein breakdown. Dose-response effects on leucine metabolism in postabsorptive men.</title>
		<year>1985</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, K. L. Minaker, John W. Rowe, M. N. Goodman, Dwight E. Matthews, Dennis M. Bier, V. R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Clinical Investigation</jconf>
		<id>W2025421578</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Carbon dioxide (CO &lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; ) levels this century will alter the protein, micronutrients, and vitamin content of rice grains with potential health consequences for the poorest rice-dependent countries</title>
		<year>2018</year>
		<authors>Chunwu Zhu, Kazuhiko Kobayashi, Irakli Loladze, Jianguo Zhu, Qian Jiang, Xi Xu, Gang Liu, Saman Seneweera, Kristie L. Ebi, Adam Drewnowski, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Lewis H. Ziska</authors>
		<jconf>Science Advances</jconf>
		<id>W2804845600</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>High-carbohydrate, high-fiber diets increase peripheral insulin sensitivity in healthy young and old adults</title>
		<year>1990</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, JW Anderson, Gilbert R. Hageman, VR Young, K. L. Minaker</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W1917700994</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Combining the effects of increased atmospheric carbon dioxide on protein, iron, and zinc availability and projected climate change on global diets: a modelling study</title>
		<year>2019</year>
		<authors>Robert Beach, Timothy B. Sulser, Allison Crimmins, Nicola Cenacchi, Jefferson Cole, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Daniel Mason-D’Croz, Samuel S. Myers, Marcus C. Sarofim, Matthew R. Smith, Lewis H. Ziska</authors>
		<jconf>The Lancet Planetary Health</jconf>
		<id>W2960289096</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>The Relationship of Strength to Function in the Older Adult</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Michael G. Brown, David R. Sinacore, Helen H. Host</authors>
		<jconf>The Journals of Gerontology Series A</jconf>
		<id>W2035011145</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>The insulinotropic actions of glucose-dependent insulinotropic polypeptide (GIP) and glucagon-like peptide-1 (7–37) in normal and diabetic subjects</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<authors>Dariush Elahi, M. McAloon-Dyke, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Graydon S. Meneilly, Anne Sclater, Kenneth L. Minaker, Joel F. Habener, Dana K. Andersen</authors>
		<jconf>Regulatory Peptides</jconf>
		<id>W2074956966</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Effect of age on body composition and resting metabolic rate</title>
		<year>1990</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Linda G. Bandini, James B. Young</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W2150045380</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Body Composition and Energy Expenditure in Adolescents with Cerebral Palsy or Myelodysplasia</title>
		<year>1991</year>
		<authors>Linda G. Bandini, Dale A. Schoeller, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Linda Wykes, William H. Dietz</authors>
		<jconf>Pediatric Research</jconf>
		<id>W1975670948</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Assessing nanotoxicity in cells &lt;i&gt;in vitro&lt;/i&gt;</title>
		<year>2009</year>
		<authors>Jedd Hillegass, Arti Shukla, Sherrill A. Lathrop, Maximilian B. MacPherson, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Brooke T. Mossman</authors>
		<jconf>Wiley Interdisciplinary Reviews Nanomedicine and Nanobiotechnology</jconf>
		<id>W2117952964</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>A Lipidomics Analysis of the Relationship Between Dietary Fatty Acid Composition and Insulin Sensitivity in Young Adults</title>
		<year>2012</year>
		<authors>C. Lawrence Kien, Janice Y. Bunn, Matthew E. Poynter, Robert Stevens, James R. Bain, Olga Ikayeva, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Catherine M. Champagne, Karen I. Crain, Timothy R. Koves, Deborah M. Muoio</authors>
		<jconf>Diabetes</jconf>
		<id>W2144946248</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>A multi-glycomic platform for the analysis of food carbohydrates</title>
		<year>2024</year>
		<authors>Garret Couture, Shawn Ehlers Cheang, Christopher Suarez, Ye Chen, Nikita P. Bacalzo, Jiani Jiang, Cheng-Yu Weng, A. Stacy, Juan J. Castillo, Omar Delannoy-Bruno, Daniel M. Webber, Michael J. Barratt, Jeffrey I. Gordon, David A. Mills, J. Bruce German, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Carlito B. Lebrilla</authors>
		<jconf>Nature Protocols</jconf>
		<id>W4400778941</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Increased Atrial and Brain Natriuretic Peptides in Adults With Cyanotic Congenital Heart Disease</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<authors>William E. Hopkins, Zengyi Chen, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Christian Hall, Harm J. Knot, Martin M. LeWinter</authors>
		<jconf>Circulation</jconf>
		<id>W2046459336</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Validation of the tracer-balance concept with reference to leucine: 24-h intravenous tracer studies with L-[1-13C]leucine and [15N-15N]urea</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<authors>AE El-Khoury, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Melchor Sánchez Mendiola, RH Tsay, RE Gleason, TE Chapman, VR Young</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W2119574872</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Allergy-related proctocolitis in infants: diagnostic usefulness of rectal biopsy.</title>
		<year>1990</year>
		<authors>Harland S. Winter, D A Antonioli, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Manuel A. Marcial, Harvey Goldman</authors>
		<jconf>PubMed</jconf>
		<id>W149433977</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Down-regulation of Manganese-Superoxide Dismutase through Phosphorylation of FOXO3a by Akt in Explanted Vascular Smooth Muscle Cells from Old Rats</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<authors>Muyao Li, Jen‐Fu Chiu, Brooke T. Mossman, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Biological Chemistry</jconf>
		<id>W2074680129</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Insulin dose-dependent reductions in plasma amino acids in man</title>
		<year>1986</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, K. L. Minaker, V. R. Young, John W. Rowe</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W2416537695</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Improving natural product research translation: From source to clinical trial</title>
		<year>2019</year>
		<authors>Barbara C. Sorkin, Adam J. Kuszak, Gregory Bloss, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Freddie Ann Hoffman, Mahtab Jafari, Bruce Barrett, Paula N. Brown, Frederic D. Bushman, Steven Casper, Floyd H. Chilton, Christopher S. Coffey, Mário G. Ferruzzi, D. Craig Hopp, Máiréad Kiely, Daniël Lakens, John B. MacMillan, David Meltzer, Marco Pahor, Jeffrey Paul, Kathleen R. Pritchett‐Corning, Sara K. Quinney, Barbara Rehermann, Kenneth D.R. Setchell, Nisha S. Sipes, Jacqueline M. Stephens, D. Lansing Taylor, Hervé Tiriac, Michael A. Walters, Dan Xi, Giovanna Zappalà, Guido F. Pauli</authors>
		<jconf>The FASEB Journal</jconf>
		<id>W2996402632</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Terms and nomenclature used for plant-derived components in nutrition and related research: efforts toward harmonization</title>
		<year>2019</year>
		<authors>Jan Frank, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Anna Rita Bilia, Elizabeth J. Johnson, Oran Kwon, Vish Prakash, Teruo Miyazawa, Michael N. Clifford, Colin D. Kay, Alan Crozier, John W. Erdman, Andrew Shao, Gary Williamson</authors>
		<jconf>Nutrition Reviews</jconf>
		<id>W2989926507</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Dietary fiber, starch, and sugars in bananas at different stages of ripeness in the retail market</title>
		<year>2021</year>
		<authors>Katherine M. Phillips, Ryan C. McGinty, Garret Couture, Pamela Pehrsson, Kyle McKillop, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>PLoS ONE</jconf>
		<id>W3182774107</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>USDA’s FoodData Central: what is it and why is it needed today?</title>
		<year>2021</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Kyle McKillop, Pamela Pehrsson, Alanna Moshfegh, James M. Harnly, John W. Finley</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W4200059582</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Valuing the Diversity of Research Methods to Advance Nutrition Science</title>
		<year>2022</year>
		<authors>Richard D. Mattes, Sylvia Rowe, Sarah D. Ohlhorst, Andrew W. Brown, Daniël J. Hoffman, DeAnn Liska, Edith J. M. Feskens, Jaapna Dhillon, Katherine L. Tucker, Leonard H. Epstein, Lynnette M. Neufeld, Michael J. Kelley, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Roger A. Sunde, Steven H. Zeisel, Anthony J. Basile, Laura Borth, Emahlea Jackson</authors>
		<jconf>Advances in Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W4225343776</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Perspective: A Research Roadmap about Ultra-Processed Foods and Human Health for the United States Food System: Proceedings from an Interdisciplinary, Multi-Stakeholder Workshop</title>
		<year>2023</year>
		<authors>Lauren E. O’Connor, Kelly Higgins, Katarina Smiljanec, Robert Bergia, Andrew W. Brown, David J. Baer, Cindy D. Davis, Mário G. Ferruzzi, Kevin H. Miller, Sylvia Rowe, Janice M.W. Rueda, Aline Andres, Sean B. Cash, John N. Coupland, Meghan Crimmins, Chelsey Fiecke, Ciarán G. Forde, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Kevin D. Hall, Bruce R. Hamaker, Kirsten Herrick, Julie Hess, Lise A.J. Heuven, Filippa Juul, Fiona C. Malcomson, Eurídice Martinez Steele, Richard D. Mattes, Mark Messina, Alyson E. Mitchell, Fang Fang Zhang</authors>
		<jconf>Advances in Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W4386799647</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Muscle Function and Mobility Biomechanics in the Elderly: An Overview of Some Recent Research</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Albert B. Schultz</authors>
		<jconf>The Journals of Gerontology Series A</jconf>
		<id>W2029792399</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Leucine metabolism in aging humans: effect of insulin and substrate availability</title>
		<year>1989</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, K. L. Minaker, V. R. Young, Dwight E. Matthews, Dennis M. Bier, John W. Rowe</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W2414387362</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Age-Related Changes in Redox Signaling and VSMC Function</title>
		<year>2009</year>
		<authors>Muyao Li, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Antioxidants and Redox Signaling</jconf>
		<id>W1973326040</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>The National Clinical Care Commission Report to Congress: Leveraging Federal Policies and Programs to Prevent Diabetes in People With Prediabetes</title>
		<year>2023</year>
		<authors>John M. Boltri, Howard Tracer, David Strogatz, Shannon Idzik, Pat Schumacher, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Ellen Leake, Clydette Powell, Donald Shell, Samuel S. Wu, William H. Herman</authors>
		<jconf>Diabetes Care</jconf>
		<id>W4318162979</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Sex-related differences in methionine metabolism and plasma homocysteine concentrations</title>
		<year>2000</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Julie Martin, Alexander Wurthmann, Amy H Prue, David B. Ebenstein, Bruce O’Rourke</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W1920696740</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Measurement of Homocysteine Concentrations and Stable Isotope Tracer Enrichments in Human Plasma</title>
		<year>1999</year>
		<authors>Michael J. MacCoss, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Dwight E. Matthews</authors>
		<jconf>Analytical Chemistry</jconf>
		<id>W1988082168</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>The 24-h pattern and rate of leucine oxidation, with particular reference to tracer estimates of leucine requirements in healthy adults</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<authors>AE El-Khoury, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Melchor Sánchez Mendiola, RH Tsay, R E Gleason, TE Chapman, VR Young</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W2152106053</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Plasma methionine and cysteine kinetics in response to an intravenous glutathione infusion in adult humans</title>
		<year>1996</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, A. M. Ajami, V. R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W1271996592</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Asbestos induces mitochondrial DNA damage and dysfunction linked to the development of apoptosis</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<authors>Arti Shukla, Michael Jung, Maria Stern, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Douglas J. Taatjes, Dennis E. Sawyer, Bennett Van Houten, Brooke T. Mossman</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Lung Cellular and Molecular Physiology</jconf>
		<id>W2150327080</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Aging: Is Oxidative Stress a Marker or Is It Causal?</title>
		<year>1999</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Proceedings of The Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine</jconf>
		<id>W2083345303</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Short‐Term Effects of Dietary Fatty Acids on Muscle Lipid Composition and Serum Acylcarnitine Profile in Human Subjects</title>
		<year>2010</year>
		<authors>C. Lawrence Kien, Karen Everingham, Robert Stevens, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Deborah M. Muoio</authors>
		<jconf>Obesity</jconf>
		<id>W2056763011</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Soy Biodiesel and Petrodiesel Emissions Differ in Size, Chemical Composition and Stimulation of Inflammatory Responses in Cells and Animals</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Muyao Li, Matthew E. Poynter, Brian C. Palmer, Erin Parker, John Kasumba, Britt A. Holmén</authors>
		<jconf>Environmental Science &amp; Technology</jconf>
		<id>W2089296760</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>The National Clinical Care Commission Report to Congress: Leveraging Federal Policies and Programs for Population-Level Diabetes Prevention and Control: Recommendations From the National Clinical Care Commission</title>
		<year>2023</year>
		<authors>Dean Schillinger, Ann Bullock, Clydette Powell, Naomi K. Fukagawa, M. Carol Greenlee, Jana Towne, Jasmine D. Gonzalvo, Aaron M. Lopata, J. William Cook, William H. Herman</authors>
		<jconf>Diabetes Care</jconf>
		<id>W4318163018</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Macronutrient Utilization After Short-term Fasting in Older and Younger Men and Women, a Pilot Study</title>
		<year>2025</year>
		<authors>San Wang, Rita Tsay, Dapeng Zhang, Daniel Ferreira da Cunha, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Research Square (Research Square)</jconf>
		<id>W4407702688</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>The 24-h kinetics of leucine oxidation in healthy adults receiving a generous leucine intake via three discrete meals</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>AE El-Khoury, Melchor Sánchez Mendiola, Naomi K. Fukagawa, RE Gleason, RH Tsay, VR Young</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W2268402281</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Methionine and cysteine kinetics at different intakes of methionine and cystine in elderly men and women</title>
		<year>1998</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Yong-Ming Yu, Vernon R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W2109811121</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Longitudinal Weight Changes, Length of Survival, and Energy Requirements of Long Term Care Residents with Dementia</title>
		<year>1997</year>
		<authors>San Y. Wang, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Monir Hossain, Wee Lock Ooi</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of the American Geriatrics Society</jconf>
		<id>W1994115742</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Measurement of intracellular sulfur amino acid metabolism in humans</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<authors>Michael J. MacCoss, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Dwight E. Matthews</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W173001419</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Oxidation of glutamine by the splanchnic bed in humans</title>
		<year>2000</year>
		<authors>Michael Haisch, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Dwight E. Matthews</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W2130400411</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Methionine and cysteine kinetics at different intakes of cystine in healthy adult men</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<authors>Tatsuo Hiramatsu, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Júlio Sérgio Marchini, Joaquin Cortiella, YM Yu, TE Chapman, VR Young</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W2110569366</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Age‐related differences in insulin‐like growth factor‐1 receptor signaling regulates Akt/FOXO3a and ERK/Fos pathways in vascular smooth muscle cells</title>
		<year>2008</year>
		<authors>Muyao Li, Jen‐Fu Chiu, Jessica Gagne, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Cellular Physiology</jconf>
		<id>W1999302601</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Protein and amino acid supplementation in older humans</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Amino Acids</jconf>
		<id>W1968908468</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Lipidomic evidence that lowering the typical dietary palmitate to oleate ratio in humans decreases the leukocyte production of proinflammatory cytokines and muscle expression of redox-sensitive genes</title>
		<year>2015</year>
		<authors>C. Lawrence Kien, Janice Y. Bunn, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Vikas Anathy, Dwight E. Matthews, Karen I. Crain, David B. Ebenstein, Emily K. Tarleton, Richard E. Pratley, Matthew E. Poynter</authors>
		<jconf>The Journal of Nutritional Biochemistry</jconf>
		<id>W1470307380</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>The National Clinical Care Commission Report to Congress: Recommendations to Better Leverage Federal Policies and Programs to Prevent and Control Diabetes</title>
		<year>2023</year>
		<authors>William H. Herman, Dean Schillinger, Shari Bolen, John M. Boltri, Ann Bullock, William H Chong, Paul R. Conlin, J. William Cook, Ayotunde O. Dokun, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Jasmine D. Gonzalvo, M. Carol Greenlee, Meredith Hawkins, Shannon Idzik, Ellen Leake, Barbara Linder, Aaron M. Lopata, Pat Schumacher, Donald Shell, David Strogatz, Jana Towne, Howard Tracer, Samuel S. Wu</authors>
		<jconf>Diabetes Care</jconf>
		<id>W4318162953</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Nucleobindin 2 inhibits senescence in gastric carcinoma</title>
		<year>2024</year>
		<authors>Yu Ishibashi, Takashi Itoh, Yasuko Oguri, Miki Hashimura, Ako Yokoi, Toshihide Matsumoto, Yohei Harada, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Misato Hayashi, Mototsugu Ono, Chika Kusano, Makoto Saegusa</authors>
		<jconf>Scientific Reports</jconf>
		<id>W4397021694</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Increased Prevalence of Mitochondrial DNA Deletions in Skeletal Muscle of Older Individuals With Impaired Glucose Tolerance: Possible Marker of Glycemic Stress</title>
		<year>1997</year>
		<authors>Ping Liang, Virginia Hughes, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Diabetes</jconf>
		<id>W2113754802</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Sarcopenia in Aging Humans: The Impact of Menopause and Disease</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Éric T. Poehlman, Michael J. Toth, Paul S. Fishman, Peter Vaitkevicius, S. S. Gottlieb, Michael L. Fisher, Tekum Fonong</authors>
		<jconf>The Journals of Gerontology Series A</jconf>
		<id>W2001913417</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Aging and high concentrations of glucose potentiate injury to mitochondrial DNA</title>
		<year>1999</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Muyao Li, Ping Liang, James C. Russell, Burton E. Sobel, P. Marlene Absher</authors>
		<jconf>Free Radical Biology and Medicine</jconf>
		<id>W2053340707</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Functional Consequences of Sarcopenia: Effects on Thermoregulation</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, W. Larry Kenney, E. R. Buskirk</authors>
		<jconf>The Journals of Gerontology Series A</jconf>
		<id>W2014512264</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Loss of Skeletal Muscle Mass With Aging: Effect on Glucose Tolerance</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, W. M. Kohrt, J. O. Holloszy</authors>
		<jconf>The Journals of Gerontology Series A</jconf>
		<id>W1980066430</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Effects of recombinant human IGF-I on glucose and leucine kinetics in men</title>
		<year>1993</year>
		<authors>Dariush Elahi, M. McAloon-Dyke, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Anne Sclater, Gail A. Wong, Richard P. Shannon, K. L. Minaker, John J. Miles, A. H. Rubenstein, C. Vandepol, al. et</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W2289093623</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Glucose and amino acid metabolism in aging man: Differential effects of insulin</title>
		<year>1988</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Kenneth L. Minaker, John W. Rowe, Dwight E. Matthews, Dennis M. Bier, Vernon R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W1972315207</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Sparing of Methionine Requirements: Evaluation of Human Data Takes Sulfur Amino Acids Beyond Protein</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W1842443111</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Protein requirements: methodologic controversy amid a call for change</title>
		<year>2014</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W2113527972</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>FoodData Central, USDA’s Updated Approach to Food Composition Data Systems</title>
		<year>2021</year>
		<authors>Kyle McKillop, James M. Harnly, Pamela Pehrsson, Naomi K. Fukagawa, John W. Finley</authors>
		<jconf>Current Developments in Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W3166981553</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Interaction between membranous &lt;scp&gt;EBP50&lt;/scp&gt; and myosin 9 as a favorable prognostic factor in ovarian clear cell carcinoma</title>
		<year>2023</year>
		<authors>Mayu Nakagawa, Toshihide Matsumoto, Ako Yokoi, Miki Hashimura, Yasuko Oguri, Ryo Konno, Yu Ishibashi, Takashi Ito, Kensuke Ohhigata, Yohei Harada, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Yoshio Kodera, Makoto Saegusa</authors>
		<jconf>Molecular Oncology</jconf>
		<id>W4385563411</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Identification and characterization of an Nrf2‐mediated ARE upstream of the rat glutamate cysteine ligase catalytic subunit gene (&lt;i&gt;GCLC&lt;/i&gt;)</title>
		<year>2009</year>
		<authors>Muyao Li, Jen‐Fu Chiu, Anne Kelsen, Shelly C. Lu, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Cellular Biochemistry</jconf>
		<id>W2021372143</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Differential activation of the inflammasome in THP-1 cells exposed to chrysotile asbestos and Libby “six-mix” amphiboles and subsequent activation of BEAS-2B cells</title>
		<year>2012</year>
		<authors>Muyao Li, Mickey E. Gunter, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Cytokine</jconf>
		<id>W2082202422</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Similar 24-h Pattern and Rate of Carbon Dioxide Production, by Indirect Calorimetry vs. Stable Isotope Dilution, in Healthy Adults under Standardized Metabolic Conditions</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<authors>Antoine E. El-Khoury, Melchor Sánchez Mendiola, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Ray E. Gleason, Vernon R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W1797808836</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Estimation of energy requirements in persons with severe central nervous system impairment</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>Linda G. Bandini, Heidi Puelzl-Quinn, Julie Morelli, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>The Journal of Pediatrics</jconf>
		<id>W1984927670</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Comprehensive oligosaccharide profiling of commercial almond milk, soy milk, and soy flour</title>
		<year>2022</year>
		<authors>Yu-Ping Huang, Bruna Paviani, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Katherine M. Phillips, Daniela Barile</authors>
		<jconf>Food Chemistry</jconf>
		<id>W4312058682</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Combined Alcohol Soluble Carbohydrate Determination (CASCADE) of Food</title>
		<year>2024</year>
		<authors>Shawn Ehlers Cheang, Jiani Jiang, Christopher Suárez, Cheng-Yu Weng, Garret Couture, Nikita P. Bacalzo, Katherine M. Phillips, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Carlito B. Lebrilla</authors>
		<jconf>ACS Food Science &amp; Technology</jconf>
		<id>W4391836476</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Nutrients and non-essential metals in darkibor kale grown at urban and rural farms: A pilot study</title>
		<year>2024</year>
		<authors>Brent F. Kim, Sara N. Lupolt, Raychel Santo, Grace H. Bachman, Xudong Zhu, Tianbao Yang, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Matthew L. Richardson, Carrie Green, Katherine M. Phillips, Keeve E. Nachman</authors>
		<jconf>PLoS ONE</jconf>
		<id>W4394856431</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Relationship of Age-Related Decreases in Muscle Mass and Strength to Skeletal Status</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Robert Marcus</authors>
		<jconf>The Journals of Gerontology Series A</jconf>
		<id>W2059647414</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Factors that Impact Susceptibility to Fiber-Induced Health Effects</title>
		<year>2011</year>
		<authors>Jennifer E. Below, Nancy J. Cox, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Ari Hirvonen, Joseph R. Testa</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Toxicology and Environmental Health Part B</jconf>
		<id>W2059981766</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Establishing health benefits of bioactive food components: a basic research scientist’s perspective</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<authors>Rumana Yasmeen, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Thomas Ty Wang</authors>
		<jconf>Current Opinion in Biotechnology</jconf>
		<id>W2569142897</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Perspective: US Documentation and Regulation of Human Nutrition Randomized Controlled Trials</title>
		<year>2020</year>
		<authors>Connie M. Weaver, Naomi K. Fukagawa, DeAnn Liska, Richard D. Mattes, Gregory Matuszek, Jeri W. Nieves, Sue A. Shapses, Linda Snetselaar</authors>
		<jconf>Advances in Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W3101991416</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Protein and amino acids</title>
		<year>2020</year>
		<authors>Yong‐Ming Yu, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Elsevier eBooks</jconf>
		<id>W3044115470</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>PTEN overexpression and nuclear β-catenin stabilization promote morular differentiation through induction of epithelial–mesenchymal transition and cancer stem cell-like properties in endometrial carcinoma</title>
		<year>2022</year>
		<authors>Ako Yokoi, Marina Minami, Miki Hashimura, Yasuko Oguri, Toshihide Matsumoto, Yoshinori Hasegawa, Mayu Nakagawa, Yu Ishibashi, Takashi Ito, Kensuke Ohhigata, Youhei Harada, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Makoto Saegusa</authors>
		<jconf>Cell Communication and Signaling</jconf>
		<id>W4309657301</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Plasma amino acid kinetics during acute states of glucagon deficiency and excess in healthy adults</title>
		<year>1990</year>
		<authors>Charles Couet, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Dwight E. Matthews, Dennis M. Bier, V. R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W1758030804</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Protein and Amino Acid Metabolism and Requirements in Older Persons</title>
		<year>1987</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Vernon R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>Clinics in Geriatric Medicine</jconf>
		<id>W112309603</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Age affects ERK1/2 and NRF2 signaling in the regulation of GCLC expression</title>
		<year>2005</year>
		<authors>Muyao Li, Rui‐Ming Liu, Cynthia R. Timblin, Suzanne G. Meyer, Brooke T. Mossman, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Cellular Physiology</jconf>
		<id>W2085708858</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Disability-adjusted life years due to chronic and hidden hunger under food system evolution with climate change and adaptation to 2050</title>
		<year>2021</year>
		<authors>Timothy B. Sulser, Robert Beach, Keith Wiebe, Shahnila Dunston, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Clinical Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W3162922423</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Multi-Glycomic Characterization of Fiber from AOAC Methods Defines the Carbohydrate Structures</title>
		<year>2022</year>
		<authors>Garret Couture, Devanand L. Luthria, Ye Chen, Nikita P. Bacalzo, Fakir Shahidullah Tareq, James M. Harnly, Katherine M. Phillips, Pamela Pehrsson, Kyle McKillop, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Carlito B. Lebrilla</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Agricultural and Food Chemistry</jconf>
		<id>W4308485015</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Nucleobindin-2 Mediates Transforming Growth Factor-β1–Driven Phenotypes in Zinc Finger E-Box Binding Homeobox 1–High Uterine Carcinosarcoma</title>
		<year>2023</year>
		<authors>Yui Kobayashi, Ako Yokoi, Miki Hashimura, Yasuko Oguri, Ryo Konno, Toshihide Matsumoto, Masataka Tochimoto, Mayu Nakagawa, Yu Ishibashi, Takashi Ito, Kensuke Ohhigata, Yohei Harada, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Yoshio Kodera, Makoto Saegusa</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal Of Pathology</jconf>
		<id>W4375951748</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>An Extracellular Signal–Regulated Kinase 2 Survival Pathway Mediates Resistance of Human Mesothelioma Cells to Asbestos-Induced Injury</title>
		<year>2011</year>
		<authors>Arti Shukla, Trisha F. Barrett, Maximilian B. MacPherson, Jedd Hillegass, Naomi K. Fukagawa, William A. Swain, Kenneth J. O’Byrne, Joseph R. Testa, Harvey I. Pass, Stephen P. Faux, Brooke T. Mossman</authors>
		<jconf>American Journal of Respiratory Cell and Molecular Biology</jconf>
		<id>W2090354536</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Dietary Fiber to Starch Ratio Affects Bovine Milk Oligosaccharide Profiles</title>
		<year>2022</year>
		<authors>Sierra D. Durham, Danielle G. Lemay, Zhe Wei, K. F. Kalscheur, John W. Finley, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Daniela Barile</authors>
		<jconf>Current Developments in Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W4214638490</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>High Glucose Concentrations Induce Oxidative Damage to Mitochondrial DNA in Explanted Vascular Smooth Muscle Cells</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<authors>Muyao Li, P. Marlene Absher, Ping Liang, James C. Russell, Burton E. Sobel, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Experimental Biology and Medicine</jconf>
		<id>W2260901544</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Modulation of cell injury and survival by high glucose and advancing age</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Free Radical Biology and Medicine</jconf>
		<id>W2027635130</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Protein and Energy Interactions Throughout Life&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;</title>
		<year>1991</year>
		<authors>Vernon R. Young, YONG‐MING YU, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Acta Paediatrica</jconf>
		<id>W2114183358</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Age‐related differences in MAP kinase activity in VSMC in response to glucose or TNF‐α</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<authors>Muyao Li, Brooke T. Mossman, Emily Kolpa, Cynthia R. Timblin, Arti Shukla, Douglas J. Taatjes, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Cellular Physiology</jconf>
		<id>W1971572733</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Advancing Age and Other Factors Influencing the Balance between Amino Acid Requirements and Toxicity</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Richard A. Galbraith</authors>
		<jconf>Journal of Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W2167283850</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Reactive Oxidative Species and Speciated Particulate Light-Duty Engine Emissions from Diesel and Biodiesel Fuel Blends</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<authors>Britt A. Holmén, Benjamin Rukavina, John Kasumba, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Energy &amp; Fuels</jconf>
		<id>W2733953112</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Petrodiesel and waste grease biodiesel (B20) emission particles at a rural recycling center: characterization and effects on lung epithelial cells and macrophages</title>
		<year>2014</year>
		<authors>Nora Traviss, Muyao Li, Melissa A. Lombard, Brett Amy Thelen, Brian C. Palmer, Matthew E. Poynter, Brooke T. Mossman, Britt A. Holmén, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Air Quality Atmosphere &amp; Health</jconf>
		<id>W2141720180</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Sex-specific metabolic adaptations from in utero exposure to particulate matter derived from combustion of petrodiesel and biodiesel fuels</title>
		<year>2023</year>
		<authors>Thomas L. Jetton, Oban T. Galbraith, Mina Peshavaria, Elizabeth A. Bonney, Britt A. Holmén, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Chemosphere</jconf>
		<id>W4387881309</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>EBP50 Depletion and Nuclear β-Catenin Accumulation Engender Aggressive Behavior of Colorectal Carcinoma through Induction of Tumor Budding</title>
		<year>2023</year>
		<authors>タカシ イトウ, Yu Ishibashi, Yasuko Oguri, Miki Hashimura, Ako Yokoi, Yohei Harada, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Misato Hayashi, Mototsugu Ono, Chika Kusano, Makoto Saegusa</authors>
		<jconf>Cancers</jconf>
		<id>W4390403415</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Plasma tryptophan and total neutral amino acid levels in men: Influence of hyperinsulinemia and age</title>
		<year>1987</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Kenneth L. Minaker, John W. Rowe, Vernon R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W2043462497</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Inhaled Asbestos Exacerbates Atherosclerosis in Apolipoprotein E–Deficient Mice via CD4 &lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; T Cells</title>
		<year>2008</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Muyao Li, Tara Sabo‐Attwood, Cynthia R. Timblin, Kelly J. Butnor, Jessica Gagne, Chad Steele, Douglas J. Taatjes, Sally A. Huber, Brooke T. Mossman</authors>
		<jconf>Environmental Health Perspectives</jconf>
		<id>W2091553216</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Plant Sulfur Compounds and Human Health</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<authors>Joseph M. Jez, Naomi K. Fukagawa</authors>
		<jconf>Agronomy monograph/Agronomy</jconf>
		<id>W132473403</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Identification of High and Low Branched-Chain Fatty Acid–Producing Phenotypes in Holstein Cows following High-Forage and Low-Forage Diets in a Crossover Designed Trial</title>
		<year>2022</year>
		<authors>Matthew J. Picklo, K. F. Kalscheur, Andrew Magnuson, Michael R. Bukowski, James M. Harnly, Naomi K. Fukagawa, John W. Finley</authors>
		<jconf>Current Developments in Nutrition</jconf>
		<id>W4210570531</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Quantitative Bottom-Up Glycomic Analysis of Polysaccharides in Food Matrices Using Liquid Chromatography–Tandem Mass Spectrometry</title>
		<year>2022</year>
		<authors>Nikita P. Bacalzo, Garret Couture, Ye Chen, Juan J. Castillo, Katherine M. Phillips, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Carlito B. Lebrilla</authors>
		<jconf>Analytical Chemistry</jconf>
		<id>W4312061212</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Diurnal pattern of the interrelationships among leucine oxidation, urea production, and hydrolysis in humans</title>
		<year>1996</year>
		<authors>A. E. el-Khoury, A. M. Ajami, Naomi K. Fukagawa, T. E. Chapman, V. R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W2418932931</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Acute effects of fructose and glucose ingestion with and without caffeine in young and old humans</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>Naomi K. Fukagawa, Helen Veirs, Gail Langeloh</authors>
		<jconf>Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W2086683759</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Dose-Dependent Responses of I3C and DIM on T-Cell Activation in the Human T Lymphocyte Jurkat Cell Line</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<authors>Man Liu, Rumana Yasmeen, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Liangli Yu, Young Ho Kim, Thomas J. Wang</authors>
		<jconf>International Journal of Molecular Sciences</jconf>
		<id>W2733734673</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Individual Variabilities in Adipose Stem Cell Proliferation, Gene Expression and Responses to Lipopolysaccharide Stimulation</title>
		<year>2022</year>
		<authors>Rumana Yasmeen, Quynhchi Pham, Naomi K. Fukagawa, Thomas T. Y. Wang</authors>
		<jconf>International Journal of Molecular Sciences</jconf>
		<id>W4306838537</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Whole body protein synthesis in healthy adult humans: 13CO2 technique vs. plasma precursor approach</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<authors>A. E. el-Khoury, Melchor Sánchez Mendiola, Naomi K. Fukagawa, V. R. Young</authors>
		<jconf>AJP Endocrinology and Metabolism</jconf>
		<id>W2300083393</id>
		<label>0</label>
		<organization>null</organization>
	</publication>
</person>